I think they will move towards town, or the chain.
So we are in the middle of town?
No we have a bit into the main street itself.
- Okay.
Imagine: We would move here, now we're here.
Now he sent a picture, next it will be Pin Location.
Then we should be done with each means of transport.
We sit in the taxi then.
- Yes we can do that.
Do you understand what I mean?
We have to chance first.
Yes.
- Otherwise we will not be able to five.
To chance in one direction yes.
- I think we should chance inward towards the batter.
Yes but then we do.
He goes with the jeans in the knee and has a string on?
What the hell...
Now we are close to land and Jonas wrote that they are waiting for us on land.
So I'm not sure how to solve that situation.
We have to hide down there I think because I have to pee too.
Should we pee and wait down there?
The first activity I go boat and they know where you go off and off.
It's so damn hard.
It is much more difficult than you think.
You hear how the police come after Lucas now, he has been in ... riots.
We have taken the wrong cathedral first.
They have been farthest farthest over there.
The station is located just as well.